SATRIA RAHMAT MUSYARIFIN BACKEND & AUTOMATION DEVELOPER

South Jakarta, Indonesia | +62 81251389915 | sumgmng@gmail.com | Linkedin | Github

PROFILE

Experienced backend and automation developer with 3 years of work experience focused on efficiency, scalability and security. As a developer, I am open to work in backend, automation environments, cybersecurity or even fraud team environments with various skills that I have learned in the description below.

SKILLS

- Backend Developer
- Automation/Scraping

- Reverse Engineering
- Cyber Security

TOOLS

- Python
- JavaScript
- **TypeScript**
- PHP Native
- Java Native
- Express Js
- Golang Native
- Selenium
- Flask
- Django
- MongoDB
- **SQL**
- CSS
- BeautifulSoup
- Requests Html

- PyTelegramBotAPI
- Undetected ChromeDriver
- Puppeteer
- WhiskeyScoket
- Pandas Git
- Linux
- Threading

- Postman
- Docker
- Jadx
- Adb
- Frida
- Burpsuite
- Paramiko
- Magisk Lsposed

LANGUAGE

- Indonesia (Native)
- English (Beginner)

WORK EXPERIENCE

South Jakarta

AUTOMATION DEVELOPER – AUTOBOT KARYA INDONESIA – FREELANCE REMOTE Automate submit and collect covid vaccine data on pedulilindungi.id via private API

- Create an unofficial WhatsApp API for sending messages.
- Create an API to generate and manage license key autobot products.
- Optimizing speed in the scraping process

South Jakarta

May 2022 - July 2023

July 2021 - August 2022

BACKEND DEVELOPER - ONTIME TECHNOLOGY INDONESIA - FULL TIME ONSITE

- Create a scheduler for data manipulation and sending email
- Create API (Dajngo Based) and mongodb queries to get data that is easy to consume
- Create a module for sales data report needs, etc. in the form of an Excel file
- Create a module to render emails from templates provided by the frontend team, and implement it to all emails
- Create a websocket server for seller to buyer chat and doctor to patient chat needs
- Handle all notification features such as mass notifications and reminder notifications using Firebase
- Create microservice using rust language
- Optimization of the code on the API and Library
- Create scraper tools for SEO team needs and for bank data needs

- Create whatsapp chat listener/scrapper and store it to elastic search using javascript
- Optimization of the scraper tool in terms of memory and CPU usage
- Create API flask based
- Creating an elasticsearch query for chart needs by scrapped whatsapp chats
- Creating an elasticsearch query to map a WhatsApp account across WhatsApp groups
- Optimization of the code on the API and Library
- Integrate to OpenAI for sentiment analytics WhatsApp chats

South Jakarta

BACKEND DEVELOPER - META PESONA TEKNOLOGI INDONESIA - FULL TIME REMOTE

October 2023 – Present

- Build scalable architecture for API using Django
- Create Django wrapper for handling request response and error logging
- Create a module to render emails from templates provided by the frontend team, and implement it to all emails
- Implement login SSO by Google
- Optimization of the code on the API and Library
- Create module for user payment and integrate it to doku
- Create a module for anti-fraud at the 88% discount new user event

South Jakarta

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (Automation Focused) – FREELANCE

January 2021 – Present

- My biggest achievement in the automation scope was successfully emulating encryption and signing logic of http requests on a mobile application created by a large company.
- The biggest achievement in cyber security scope is successfully finding race condition vulnerability, SQL Injection, and XSS on several
 websites which if used for crime can harm the website owner, such as adding balances, viewing or deleting, even manipulating databases and
 stealing admin cookies.
- Create Captcha solver
- Automate serve customers on <u>itemku</u>
- Automate war ticket KAI via private API
- Create a Zalora, Mapclub, and Foot Locker automation tool for getting product's detail, checkout, etc
- Create Apx The wrapper and helper for Flask
- Automate VM management on <u>IdCloudHost</u>
- Create an article scraper tool
- Automate mirroring data from <u>p-store</u> to personal website
- Create Ruangguru scraper
- Create flightradar24 scrapper
- Automate post data on <u>asuransi.partaiperindo.com</u>
- Automate <u>Indosat Simpel</u> transaction via private API as extension of <u>TigaPutri</u> using Golang
- Automate tiktok interaction
- Create Goiek transaction scrapper
- Create <u>Plagiarism Scanner</u> web based
- Automate Checkout product on BliBli and JDID
- Create Whatsapp blaster and scrapper
- Create <u>Sociolla</u> scrapper
- Automate transaction on telegram bot
- Automate <u>audiomack</u> interaction

PROJECTS

Some automation projects and fraud demonstrations can be seen through the following url https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLUR--SLLapFskSFQ5 vRjbJmoDYbw9v6

EDUCATION

SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH VOCATIONAL SCHOOL

Department of Computer and Network Engineering

Muara Badak, East Kalimantan August 2019 – Apr 2022

- Create web-based applications for grouping reading interests using Flask and Scikit-learn.
- Build a local network circuit using mikrotik.
- Automate networking via telegram using paramiko and pyTelegramBotAPI.

COURSE

- <u>Python</u> Sololearn<u>JavaScript</u> Sololearn
- PHP Sololearn
- <u>SQL</u> Sololearn
- GO Sololearn